Michael Szeto

User Interface and User Experience Designer

Get in Touch:

- 027 449 8312
- www.michaelszeto.co.nz

Career Objective:

I am a designer who is most passionate about User Interface and User Experience Design. Having experienced various industry opportunities working in corporate organisations and with multiple start ups, I am avaiable to hear about the next freelance project that will allow me to apply my skills, but will also challenge me to develop and improve myself as a designer.

Work Experience:

Pushpay- Full Time Position (2015 to Present).

Pushpay focus on building payment software to help charities and churches recieve donations faster and more effectively. I am currently begining at Pushpay as a Junior Designer and am looking foward to contributing and being a part of the Pushpay team.

Inland Revenue-Part Time Internship (2015).

My responsibilities in Inland Revenues new Information Management department included assisting the head director in developing Visual Guidelines, Infographics and collaborating with a team of junior analysts to produce better written content

New Zealand Post- Full Time Internship (2014-2015).

My main roles as an Interaction Design Intern included Rapid Prototyping on the Print Postage Online platform, UI/UX Design, Front End HTML,CSS and JQuery, User-Testing, Documentation, Graphic Design and reporting to the Head of the Online Team.

Flexitime- Part Time Contract. (2014-2015).

FlexiTime builds software that focuses on managing payroll. I worked on the launch and redesign of FlexiTimes new responsive website. My tasks included Web Design, Graphic Design, Front End HTML and CSS, UX Design and collaborating with FlexiTimes Chief-Marketing-Officer.

Lightning Lab- Full Time Contract (2014).

Lightning Lab is a 3 month accelerator program designed to help multiple start ups further their business growth. As a Design Lab Tech, my work here included UI/UX Design, Web Design, Front-End HTML and CSS, Photography, Videography and Graphic Design tasks for the multiple start up companies in the program.

Designgel- Part Time Designer (2012-2013).

Designgel is a not-for-profit organisation providing small to medium sized organisations affordable design services. I worked on multiple Web and Photography projects for various clients and worked in a small sized design team.

Technical Skills:

- . Adobe Photoshop (Advanced).
- . HTML and CSS (Advanced).
- . Bohemian Sketch (Advanced).
- . Adobe Illustrator (Intermediate).
- . Invision App (Intermediate).
- . SASS/LESS (Intermediate).
- . Javascript/JQuery (Basic).

Personal Skills:

- . Excellent time-management.
- . Works well in team environments/individually.
- . Strong communication skills.
- . Commited personality.
- . Works with an obliging manner.
- . Open minded to all possibilities.
- . Positive approach to learning new skills.

Education:

Victoria University of Wellington (2011 to 2014). *Bachelor of Design Innovation majoring in Digital Media Design.*

^{*} References are avaliable on request.